# Explanation of chances:
# chances are based on a random number between 0 and 100. With this being said
# let's say that the random number picked at the time is 50 and the chance in the config is 40
# you will not get the reward because the random number must be less than the chance in the config.


# A less random more efficient random
# Documentation: http://dsiutils.di.unimi.it/docs/it/unimi/dsi/util/XoRoShiRo128PlusRandom.html
# This is only compatible with some spigot forks and recent versions of Paper.
random-use-optimized-psuedo-random: true

grace-period: false

auto-respawn:
  enabled: true
  delay: 2

items:
  lightningwand-item:
    material: 'GOLD_HOE'
    name: '&eLightning Wand'
    lore:
      - ''
      - '&eRight click this somewhere to strike lightning!'
      - ''
      - '&eUses: &f{uses}'
      - ''
    options:
      max-iterator-distance: 48
      negative-1-keyword: '&aUNLIMITED'
  sandwand-item:
    material: 'WOOD_HOE'
    name: '&cSand Wand'
    lore:
      - ''
      - '&cRight click this to destroy all the sand in this x/y coordinate!'
      - ''
      - '&eUses: &f{uses}'
      - ''
    options:
      negative-1-keyword: '&aUNLIMITED'
  throwablecegg-item:
    material: 'MONSTER_EGG'
    data: 50
    name: '&aThrowable Creeper Egg'
    lore:
      - ''
      - ' &aRight click this egg to throw a creeper!'
      - ''
    options:
      explosion-delay: 40
      egg-name: '&cTHROWABLE CREEPER EGG'

#Header for all rewards
rewards:
  verbose-ops: false
  mining:
    only-survival: true
    event-priority: 'MONITOR'
    enabled: true
    rewards:
      #Meaningless unique identifier for the reward
      irongolem-spawner:
        #The chance to get an irongolem spawner
        chance: 10.5
        commands:
          - 'ss give {player} irongolem'
          - 'broadcast &c&l{player} HAS WON A IRONGOLEM WHILST &e&l{reward-type}'
      apple:
        chance: 4.0
        commands:
          - 'give {player} apple'
          - 'broadcast &c&l{player} HAS WON AN APPLE WHILST &e&l{reward-type}'
      killyourself:
        chance: 1.0
        commands:
          - 'kill {player}'
          - 'broadcast &c&l{player} HAS KILLED THEMSELVES WHILST &e&l{reward-type}'
      iron-ingot:
        chance: 99.0
        commands:
          - 'kill {player}'
          - 'broadcast &c&l{player} HAS BEEN GIVEN AN IRON INGOT WHILST &e&l{reward-type}'
  fishing:
    only-survival: true
    event-priority: 'MONITOR'
    enabled: true
    rewards:
      #Meaningless unique identifier for the reward
      irongolem-spawner:
        #The chance to get an irongolem spawner
        chance: 10.5
        commands:
          - 'ss give {player} irongolem'
          - 'broadcast &c&l{player} HAS WON A IRONGOLEM WHILST &e&l{reward-type}'
      apple:
        chance: 4.0
        commands:
          - 'give {player} apple'
          - 'broadcast &c&l{player} HAS WON AN APPLE WHILST &e&l{reward-type}'
      killyourself:
        chance: 1.0
        commands:
          - 'kill {player}'
          - 'broadcast &c&l{player} HAS KILLED THEMSELVES WHILST &e&l{reward-type}'
      iron-ingot:
        chance: 99.0
        commands:
          - 'kill {player}'
          - 'broadcast &c&l{player} HAS BEEN GIVEN AN IRON INGOT WHILST &e&l{reward-type}'
trivia:
  messages:
    new-trivia-question: '&8[&c&lFrontier&b&lTrivia&8] &c{question} Answer correctly to win rewards!'

  timer-in-minutes: 5
  #
  # Answer types:
  # ANY_EQUALS: The answer must in-case-sensitively match
  # ANY_CONTAINS: The answer must in-case-sensitively contain one of the Answers
  # ALL_CONTAINS: The answer must contain all of the Answers in-case-sensitively
  # ANY_REGEX_MATCHES: If any of the Answers (treated as regex patterns) match the answer
  # ALL_REGEX_MATCHES: If all of the Answers (treated as regex patterns) match the answer
  #
  questions:
    1:
      question: "Who created Minecraft?"
      display-answer: "Notch"
      answer-type: "ANY_EQUALS"
      answers: [
        "Notch"
      ]
    2:
      question: "How many owners are there?"
      display-answer: "One"
      answer-type: "ANY_EQUALS"
      answers: [
        "1",
        "One"
      ]
    3:
      question: "When was minecraft created?"
      display-answer: "May 17th 2009"
      answer-type: "ANY_EQUALS"
      answers: [
        "May 2009",
        "2009",
        "5/17/2009",
        "17/5/2009",
        "May 17th 2009"
      ]
    4:
      question: "Which 3 items are used for crafting a redstone comparator?"
      display-answer: "Stone, Quartz & Redstone torches"
      answer-type: "ALL_CONTAINS"
      answers: [
        "Stone",
        "Quartz",
        "Redstone Torch"
      ]
    5:
      question: "How much wheat is required to bake 32 cookies?"
      display-answer: "Eight"
      answer-type: "ANY_CONTAINS"
      answers: [
        "8",
        "Eight"
      ]
    6:
      question: "How many diamonds are needed to craft a full Diamond armor set?"
      display-answer: "Twenty Four"
      answer-type: "ANY_CONTAINS"
      answers: [
        "24",
        "Twenty Four"
      ]
    7:
      question: "How many items can you hold in a full inventory space?"
      display-answer: "2,304 Items"
      answer-type: "ANY_CONTAINS"
      answers: [
        "2304",
        "2,304"
      ]
    8:
      question: "What was Notch originally trying to make when he made the creeper?"
      display-answer: "Pig"
      answer-type: "ANY_CONTAINS"
      answers: [
        "Pig"
      ]
    9:
      question: "What did Minecraft used to be called?"
      display-answer: "Cave Game"
      answer-type: "ALL_CONTAINS"
      answers: [
        "Cave",
        "Game"
      ]
    10:
      question: "How many blocks can a redstone signal travel without running out of power? (with no repeaters)"
      display-answer: "15 Blocks"
      answer-type: "ANY_CONTAINS"
      answers: [
        "15",
        "fifteen"
      ]
    13:
      question: "What does Notch drop if you kill him in multiplayer, besides his inventory?"
      display-answer: "A apple"
      answer-type: "ALL_CONTAINS"
      answers: [
        "Apple"
      ]
    14:
      question: "What animal was used for the sound of a ghast?"
      display-answer: "A cat"
      answer-type: "ALL_CONTAINS"
      answers: [
        "Cat"
      ]
    15:
      question: "Has the pigman ever been removed from the game?"
      display-answer: "No"
      answer-type: "ALL_CONTAINS"
      answers: [
        "No"
      ]
    16:
      question: "What happens wwhen a creeper is struck by lighning?"
      display-answer: "It becomes charged"
      answer-type: "ALL_CONTAINS"
      answers: [
        "it",
        "becomes",
        "charged"
      ]
    17:
      question: "What is the rarest mineral in the game?"
      display-answer: "Emerald"
      answer-type: "ANY_EQUALS"
      answers: [
        "Emerald"
      ]
    18:
      question: "What film was the iron golem mob inspired by?"
      display-answer: "Laputa"
      answer-type: "ANY_EQUALS"
      answers: [
        "Laputa"
      ]
    19:
      question: "Can sugar cane be bone mealed?"
      display-answer: "No"
      answer-type: "ANY_EQUALS"
      answers: [
        "No"
      ]
    20:
      question: "How many items can be used to make potions?"
      display-answer: "13"
      answer-type: "ANY_CONTAINS"
      answers: [
        "13",
        "thirteen"
      ]
    21:
      question: "How long did it take for Minecraft to be created?"
      display-answer: "6 Days"
      answer-type: "ALL_CONTAINS"
      answers: [
        "6",
        "days"
      ]
    22:
      question: "What will stop an enderman becoming hostile when you look at it in the face?"
      display-answer: "A pumpkin"
      answer-type: "ALL_CONTAINS"
      answers: [
        "pumpkin"
      ]
    23:
      question: "Which new food does the sheep drop?"
      display-answer: "Mutton"
      answer-type: "ALL_CONTAINS"
      answers: [
        "mutton"
      ]
    24:
      question: "What two colours of clothes do zombie wear? (default resource pack)"
      display-answer: "Blue and Green"
      answer-type: "ALL_CONTAINS"
      answers: [
        "blue",
        "green"
      ]
    25:
      question: "What does the Creeper drop after you kill it?"
      display-answer: "Gunpowder"
      answer-type: "ALL_CONTAINS"
      answers: [
        "gunpowder"
      ]
    26:
      question: "What mobs scare the creeper?"
      display-answer: "Ocelot"
      answer-type: "ALL_CONTAINS"
      answers: [
        "ocelot"
      ]
    27:
      question: "At what stage of the game were ghasts added in?"
      display-answer: "Alpha"
      answer-type: "ALL_CONTAINS"
      answers: [
        "alpha"
      ]
    28:
      question: "What do skeletons use to kill players?"
      display-answer: "Bows"
      answer-type: "ALL_CONTAINS"
      answers: [
        "bows"
      ]
    29:
      question: "What do skeletons use to kill players?"
      display-answer: "Bows"
      answer-type: "ALL_CONTAINS"
      answers: [
        "bows"
      ]
    30:
      question: "How much wool is neeeded to craft a bed?"
      display-answer: "Three"
      answer-type: "ANY_CONTAINS"
      answers: [
        "3",
        "three"
      ]
    31:
      question: "What mob drops ink sacks?"
      display-answer: "Squid"
      answer-type: "ANY_CONTAINS"
      answers: [
        "squid"
      ]
    32:
      question: "What mob is known to produce demented noises?"
      display-answer: "Zombies"
      answer-type: "ANY_CONTAINS"
      answers: [
        "zombies"
      ]
    33:
      question: "In 1.8 what mob spawns in water?"
      display-answer: "Squid"
      answer-type: "ANY_CONTAINS"
      answers: [
        "squid"
      ]
    34:
      question: "What genre is minecraft?"
      display-answer: "Sandbox"
      answer-type: "ANY_CONTAINS"
      answers: [
        "sandbox"
      ]
    35:
      question: "How many hearts does a chicken have?"
      display-answer: "Four"
      answer-type: "ANY_CONTAINS"
      answers: [
        "4",
        "four"
      ]
    36:
      question: "What coding language minecraft written in?"
      display-answer: "Java"
      answer-type: "ANY_CONTAINS"
      answers: [
        "java"
      ]
    37:
      question: "What set of armour can't be crafted?"
      display-answer: "Chain"
      answer-type: "ANY_CONTAINS"
      answers: [
        "chain"
      ]
    38:
      question: "What is the second largest mob?"
      display-answer: "Ghast"
      answer-type: "ANY_CONTAINS"
      answers: [
        "ghast"
      ]
    39:
      question: "What dimension do enderman most commanly spawn in?"
      display-answer: "End"
      answer-type: "ANY_CONTAINS"
      answers: [
        "end"
      ]
    40:
      question: "What protects you from 12% of the damage?"
      display-answer: "Helmet"
      answer-type: "ANY_CONTAINS"
      answers: [
        "helmet"
      ]
    41:
      question: "How many wooden planks do you need to craft 4 sticks?"
      display-answer: "Two"
      answer-type: "ANY_CONTAINS"
      answers: [
        "2",
        "Two"
      ]
    42:
      question: "What update were shields added in?"
      display-answer: "Combat update (1.9)"
      answer-type: "ANY_CONTAINS"
      answers: [
        "1.9",
        "Combat update"
      ]
    43:
      question: "How much soul sand is needed to spawn the wither?"
      display-answer: "Four"
      answer-type: "ANY_CONTAINS"
      answers: [
        "4",
        "four"
      ]
    44:
      question: "How many minutes does it take a baby villager to grow up?"
      display-answer: "Twenty"
      answer-type: "ANY_CONTAINS"
      answers: [
        "20",
        "twenty"
      ]
    45:
      question: "What does it take to cure a zombie villager?"
      display-answer: "Potion of weakness and a golden apple"
      answer-type: "ALL_CONTAINS"
      answers: [
        "Potion of weakness",
        "golden apple"
      ]
    46:
      question: "What is the highest layer diamonds can be found at?"
      display-answer: "Sixteen"
      answer-type: "ANY_CONTAINS"
      answers: [
        "16",
        "sixteen"
      ]
    47:
      question: "How much obsidian does it take to make a nether portal?"
      display-answer: "10"
      answer-type: "ANY_CONTAINS"
      answers: [
        "10",
        "ten"
      ]
    48:
      question: "What is the smallest animal in minecraft (1.8)?"
      display-answer: "Silverfish"
      answer-type: "ANY_CONTAINS"
      answers: [
        "silverfish"
      ]
    49:
      question: "How much time does it take for tnt to explode?"
      display-answer: "4 Seconds"
      answer-type: "ANY_CONTAINS"
      answers: [
        "4 seconds",
        "4s"
      ]
    50:
      question: "What percentage does leggins protect you from?"
      display-answer: "25%"
      answer-type: "ANY_CONTAINS"
      answers: [
        "25%",
        "25"
      ]
    51:
      question: "What is the length of the End credits?"
      display-answer: "9 minutes and 28 seconds"
      answer-type: "ANY_CONTAINS"
      answers: [
        "9m 28s",
        "9minutes 28seconds",
        "9 minutes 28 seconds",
        "9 minutes and 28 seconds"
      ]
    52:
      question: "How can you disable a nether portal without breaking any blocks?"
      display-answer: "Water or Lava"
      answer-type: "ANY_CONTAINS"
      answers: [
        "water",
        "lava"
      ]
    53:
      question: "How many hearts is 1 hp?"
      display-answer: "Half a heart"
      answer-type: "ANY_CONTAINS"
      answers: [
        "half",
        "0.5",
        ".5"
      ]
    54:
      question: "Who wrote all of these new trivia questions?"
      display-answer: "Frosty"
      answer-type: "ANY_CONTAINS"
      answers: [
        "frosty"
      ]

  # Rewards
  rewards:
    1:
      chance: 25
      commands: [
        "eco give {player} 10000"
      ]
    2:
      chance: 15
      commands: [
        "eco give {player} 15000"
      ]
    3:
      chance: 3
      commands: [
        "cc give p blizzard 1 {player}"
      ]
    4:
      chance: 1.5
      commands: [
        "cc give p Godly 1 {player}"
      ]
    5:
      chance: 0.5
      commands: [
        "cc give p Tempest 1 {player}"
      ]
    6:
      chance: 10
      commands: [
        "eco give {player} 25000"
      ]
    7:
      chance: 8
      commands: [
        "eco give {player} 50000"
      ]